<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop 2019 on Black in AI</title>
    <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshop 2019 on Black in AI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Black in AI</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 17:34:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Black in AI 2019: Call for Submissions The deadline for submissions has officially passed!
We invite submissions for the Third Black in AI Workshop (co-located with NeurIPS 2019 at the Vancouver Convention Center, Vancouver CANADA. We welcome research work in artificial intelligence, computational neuroscience, and its applications.
These include, but are not limited to, deep learning, knowledge reasoning, machine learning, multi-agent systems, statistical reasoning, theory, computer vision, natural language processing, robotics, as well as applications of AI to other domains such as health and education, and submissions concerning fairness, ethics, and transparency in AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizers 2019</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/organizers/</guid>
      <description>2019 Workshop Chairs     Institution Chair of      In-Q-Tel Sponsorships &amp;amp; Logistics    Havard University Accomodations &amp;amp; Travel    Lancaster University Publicity    McGill University Accomodations &amp;amp; Travel    Automattic.com Travel Grants    Streem Inc Publications   Daniel Nkemelu Georgia Institute of Technology Sponsorships &amp;amp; Logistics    University of Alberta Recruitment    2019 Program Committee Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programs 2019</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/programs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/programs/</guid>
      <description>Schedule 2019 Coming soon&amp;hellip;
Keynote Speakers Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors 2019</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to our corporate sponsors, the workshop is free to attendees and we are able to provide inclusive travel funding to select participants.
 Diamond Sponsors Coming soon&amp;hellip;
 Platinum Sponsors Coming soon&amp;hellip;
Gold Sponsors  Coming soon&amp;hellip;
Silver Sponsors Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission Instructions 2019</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/submissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/submissions/</guid>
      <description>The deadline for submissions has officially passed!
We welcome works in artificial intelligence, including, but not limited to, computer vision, deep learning, knowledge reasoning, machine learning, multi-agent systems, natural language processing, statistical reasoning, theory, robotics, as well as applications of AI to other domains such as health and education, and submissions concerning fairness, ethics, and transparency in AI. Papers may introduce new theory, methodology, or applications.
We also welcome position papers and demos related to these areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Grants 2019</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2019/grants/</guid>
      <description>The deadline for Travel Grants has officially passed!
Need-based travel grants will be awarded to workshop participants. Participants do not need to submit a paper in order to be considered for a travel grant. The travel grant can be used for covering costs associated with the workshop such as NIPS registration, accommodation and travel. Please note that the travel grants may not cover all of your costs and we may not be able to award them to all applicants.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>