<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BAI 2018 2nd Workshop on Black in AI</title>
    <link>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BAI 2018 2nd Workshop on Black in AI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Black in AI</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizers 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/organizers/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Co-Chairs Rediet Abebe, Cornell University
[Esube Bekele](), US Naval Research Laboratory
Sarah Brown, Brown University
Mouhamadou Moustapha Cisse, Google AI
Timnit Gebru, Microsoft Research
Judy Wawira Gichoya, Oregon Health and Science University
[Devin Guillory](), Etsy
Sanmi Koyejo, University of Illinois, Urbana Champaigns
2018 Program Committee    Name Institution/Organization     Ousmane Amadou Dia Element AI   Irwan Bello Google Brain   Charles Earl Automattic   Zanele Munyikwa MIT Sloan School of Management   Oluwaseun Francis Egbelowo University of the Witwatersrand South Africa   Justice Amoh Dartmouth College   Jack Hessel Cornell University   Samy Bengio Google Brain   Abigail Jacobs University of California Berkeley   Hal DaumĂŠ III Microsoft Research / University of Maryland   Ben Green Harvard   Basiliyos Tilahun BETRU University of Yaounde I National Advanced School of Engneering   Ehi Nosakhare MIT   Dhaval Adjodah MIT Media Lab   Kale-ab Tessera University of Witwatersrand   Lily Hu Harvard University   Charles C Onu McGill University   Alvin Grissom II Ursinus College   Billy Okal Voyage   Zachary C Lipton CMU   Awa Dieng Duke University   Adji Bousso Dieng Columbia   VICTOR C DIBIA IBM Research   Rachel Thomas fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Grants 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/grants/</guid>
      <description>Travel Awards Need-based travel grants will be awarded to workshop participants. Participants do not need to submit a paper in order to be considered for a travel grant. The travel grant can be used for covering costs associated with the workshop such as NIPS registration, accommodation and travel. Please note that the travel grants may not cover all of your costs and we may not be able to award them to all applicants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission Instructions 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/submissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/submissions/</guid>
      <description>We welcome work in artificial intelligence, including, but not limited to, computer vision, deep learning, knowledge reasoning, machine learning, multi-agent systems, natural language processing, statistical reasoning, theory, robotics, as well as applications of AI to other domains such as health and education, and submissions concerning fairness, ethics, and transparency in AI. Papers may introduce new theory, methodology, or applications. We also welcome position papers and demos related to these areas. Work may be previously published, completed, or ongoing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Participation 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/ws_2018/cfp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The second Black in AI event will be co-located with &lt;a href=&#34;https://nips.cc/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;NIPS 2018&lt;/a&gt; at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://congresmtl.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Palais des Congrès de Montréal (Montreal Convention Centre)&lt;/a&gt;  in Montréal CANADA on December 7th from 1:00pm to 6:00pm. The workshop will feature invited talks from prominent researchers and practitioners, oral presentations, and a poster session. There will also be socials to facilitate networking, discussion of different career opportunities in AI, and sharing of ideas to increase participation of Black researchers in the field. We invite all members of the AI community to attend the workshop. The early registration deadline for the conference is October 24, 2018. We strongly encourage workshop attendees to register for the workshops as early as possible. The registration can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://nips.cc/accounts/login/?next=/Profile&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>